I teach crafters, and mostly women for stickers.
You teach crafters?
For themselves.
Crafters make stickers.
Okay, love it.
I love this.
This is great.
We did over seven figures last year.
I really wanna be at three million USD per year,
but my constraint is 30-day cash.
Probably costing me about $90 to acquire them
with meta-ads, so I can't scale profitably.
And the problem is that it takes you two months
to break even rather than one.
From what I've worked out,
that it's probably more like six months.
And when you're running the ads funnels,
you're running to a webinar, running to a five-day event.
What is it running to?
Three, four, five-day events.
You can very easily solve this with two steps.
Number one is that when you're doing a five-day
selling event, you need to sell the expensive thing.
300 to 600 is the impulse purchase window.
300 is the low end, 600 is the high end.
That's your range.
But you need to sell the annual upfront.
That's number one.
And what I want you to do is come up
with one to two big bonuses
that are gonna be annual exclusive.
You will dramatically increase your conversions
if you add a physical product
that makes this pitch tangible.
Add the annual, make that the only offer available.
I thought that helped.
Okay, that's really awesome.
Thanks so much.
You bet.
Talk soon, I'll see you inside the group.
All right.
Cheers.